(Sheldon:)She made spaghetti
with little hot dogs.
(Sheldon:)I like spaghetti with little hot dogs.
Well, then why did you
have Chinese food with us?
I didn't wanna upset you.
(Sheldon:)Howard made it very clear that my
allegiance should be to male comrades...
(Sheldon:)...before women who sell their bodies
for money.
(Leonard:)Is it possible he said,
"Bros before ho's"?
(Sheldon:)Yes, but I rephrased it
to avoid offending the ho's.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I don't care
if you wanna be friends with Penny.
(Penny:)Oh.
So the turmoil
that has been keeping me...
(Sheldon:)...from achieving REM sleep
was entirely unjustified?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Well, then as my meemaw would say...
(Sheldon:)...looks like we butchered a pig,
but nobody wanted bacon.
(Leonard:)I guess not.
(Sheldon:)And now, as promised, the tangent.